J. D. Sloan Photographs MS247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Born digital materials, circa 1995 -- 2013; MS247.002; 1 Linear Feet
  - Binder B, 2000 -- 2010; MS247.001500 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Tufts HAD: Hispanic Dinner Dental, 2006; MS247.001505 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      HAD: Hispanic Dinner Dental
    - 2006 Dental reunion disc 1 of 2, MS247.001506 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Rolls 1-9
    - 2006 Dental reunion disc 2 of 2, MS247.001507 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Rolls 10-A
    - Tufts 2006 Dental awards dinner, 2006 May 12; MS247.001508 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Medford Grad School 2006 Graduate Hooding, 2006 May 20; MS247.001509 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      great hood, smiling Grad School Dean 7 rolls
      Dean Guertin; Medford Campus
    - 2006 Medical reunion, 2006 May 13; MS247.001510 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Disc I Rolls 1-6 good stuff
      Jamshed; Rosenblatt; Tonto Gipstein; School of Medicine
    - 2006 Medical reunion, 2006 May 13; MS247.001511 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Disc II Rolls 7-12 good stuff
    - 2006 Bates Andrews Research Awards Dinner, 2006 May 16; MS247.001512 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      McCormick and Scmick
    - 2006 SNDA Awards Dinner Dental, 2006 May 17; MS247.001513 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      5 rolls
    - 2006 OKU Awards Dinner Tufts Dental, 2006 May 19; MS247.001514 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 2006 Dental Commencement, 2006 May; MS247.001515 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Lance Armstrong toothbrushes mortar board
    - Dental April/May 06 2006 Practive Group photos, 2006 April -- 2006 May; MS247.001516 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      2006 Practice group photos
    - 06 Grad Awards Medford, 2006; MS247.001517 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Grad School Awards
    - Dental 06 Perio at Lombardo's, 2006; MS247.001518 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      06 Perio Lombardo's
    - Dental International White coat ceremony, 2006 July 24; MS247.001519 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental oral surgery year end dinner at Colonnade, 2006 June 21; MS247.001520 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Marylin Peterson hired; School of Dental Medicine
    - Dental International White coat ceremony, 2006 July 26; MS247.001521 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 06 Dental Family welcome, 2006 August 29; MS247.001522 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      editted disc done with Mike Ritter
    - Tufts USDA Nutrition Jeffrey Blumberg, 2007 January 2; MS247.001523 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      USDA Nutrition
    - William Harper 3rd annual John Holmes Poet, 2007 April 4; MS247.001524 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 3rd annual Holmes poetry library, 2007 April 4; MS247.001525 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Whole University 2006 Fac Recognition Lunch, 2006 August 6; MS247.001526 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Disc I of II
      Christine Robertson
    - Whole University 2006 Fac Recognition Lunch, 2006 August 6; MS247.001527 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Disc II of II
    - 2nd annual Josiahober Balmuth Classics Lecture, 2007; MS247.001528 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      rolls 5820-5824 Classics Dept
      David Proctor; Miriam S. Balmuth
    - Tufts Medford Library Tisch Author Talk Frank Ackerman, 2006 October 20; MS247.001529 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      "Priceless" Parents weekend
    - Tufts Author Talk Marty Sherwin, 2006 October 10; MS247.001530 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Pulitzer winner for American Prometheus on Robt. Oppenheimer
      Kay McCarthy; Ellie Short; Sherman Teishman
    - Silvia Evangelista, 2007 March 27; MS247.001531 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Entrepreneurial Leadership Program, 2007; MS247.001532 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Business plan competition
    - Blank disc, circa 2000s; MS247.001533 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Research Day disc I of III, 2006 September 27; MS247.001534 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      First disc of 3:9394-9397
    - Tufts Research Day disc II of III, 2006 September 27; MS247.001535 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      second disc of 3:9398-9401
    - Tufts Research Day disc III of III, 2006 September 27; MS247.001536 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      third disc of 3:9402-9405
    - Tisch school screening, 2006 December 12; MS247.001537 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Margaret Lazarus faculty member,Steve Bretler's wife
    - Dental Roll A 2007 Yankee Dental, MS247.001538 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental Roll B 2007 Yankee Dental, MS247.001539 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Bates Andrews, 2007 July 3; MS247.001540 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Dental Disc I job 6244-6248
    - Bates Andrews, 2007 July 3; MS247.001541 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Dental Disc II 6249-6252
    - Dental 070310 White Coat II, circa 2010; MS247.001542 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental 070310 White Coat III, circa 2010; MS247.001543 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental Student Group Practice Photos 1-8, circa 2000s; MS247.001544 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental Memorial Reception, 2007 March 27; MS247.001545 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Silvia Evangelista
    - 2007 Dental Commencement disc I, 2007 May; MS247.001546 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 2007 Dental Commencement disc II, 2007 May; MS247.001547 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Dental Awards Dinner disc I of II, 2007 May 09; MS247.001548 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      5196-5202
    - Tufts Dental Awards Dinner disc II of II, 2007 May 09; MS247.001549 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Bates Andrews Research Dinner, 2007 May 15; MS247.001550 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      files 340-344
      Eileen Doherty; School of Dental Medicine
    - Dental 07 OKU Awards Dinner, 2007; MS247.001551 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Bob Ryan; Dr Weiner; School of Dental Medicine
    - Memorial for Dr Cyril Gaum Dentist (Fac), 2007 June 8; MS247.001552 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Disc I
    - Memorial for Dr Cyril Gaum Dentist (Fac), 2007 June 8; MS247.001553 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Disc II
    - SNDA Awards Dinner, 2007 May 16; MS247.001554 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - SNDA Awards Dinner, 2007 May 16; MS247.001555 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Medford Grad School Graduate Hooding, 2007; MS247.001556 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      5443-5447
    - Dental Surgery Dinner at Colonnade, 2007 June 20; MS247.001557 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      8875-79
    - Dental D'11 Family Welcome Day, 2007; MS247.001558 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental D'11 Family Welcome Day, 2007; MS247.001559 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental Faculty Recognition Luncheon, 2007; MS247.001560 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental Faculty Recognition Luncheon, 2007; MS247.001561 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Hispanic Dental Association Awards Ceremony, 2007 May 14; MS247.001562 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Hispanic Dental Association Awards Ceremony, 2007 May 14; MS247.001563 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dental Caroline Browning facial scarring, 2007 October 24; MS247.001564 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      18 Tremont
      Ted Basset; School of Dental Medicine
    - Library Author Talk Jonathan Wilson, 2007 October 11; MS247.001565 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Chagall revealed
    - Library Author Talk Dale Peterson's Jane Goodall, 2007 November 1; MS247.001566 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Friends Luncheon
  - Binder C, 2000 -- 2013; MS247.001567 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Archbishop Desmond Tutu, 2002 April 12; MS247.001568 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - UCCPS playground Somerville Housing Pierre Omidyar, 2003 May 17; MS247.001569 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Dining Parents Weekend, 2010 October 22; MS247.001570 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Dining Jumbo and Staff
    - Dental Family Day, 2010 September 13; MS247.001571 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Dental family Day
    - Author Talk Kareem Roustom, 2010 October 10; MS247.001572 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Tisch
    - Tisch Author Talk 11 to Borgers, 2011; MS247.001573 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Gordon Math prize
    - Dental Bates day, 2011 March 2; MS247.001574 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Disc A camera frame: 0978-1249 110 frames
    - Dental Bates day, 2011 March 2; MS247.001575 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Disc B camera frame: 1256-1505 112 frames
    - LYZA 1st shoot Brown:Blue, 2011 April 25; MS247.001576 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      patio and inside 77 items
    - TIF white coat, 2011; MS247.001577 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Robert Pinsky Holmes Lecture, 2011 April 1; MS247.001578 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Tufts: Tisch
    - Dental Bates Andrews, 2011 March 2; MS247.001579 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      year end awards, Kugel given by student researchers to Lonnie.
    - Student Practices Dental, 2011; MS247.001580 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Disc 1
    - Student Practices Dental, 2011; MS247.001581 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Disc 2 groups 1-8
      Katie Keen; Boston Campus; School of Dental Medicine
    - Sustainability Research Day, 2011 May 3; MS247.001582 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Peggy newell acting provost
    - Tufts Rob Hollister Goodbye Fete, 2011 May 5; MS247.001583 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      160 images
    - Dental Graduation awards dinner Copley Westin, 2011; MS247.001584 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      the last supper
    - Dental awards lunch, 2011 May 10; MS247.001585 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      new format
    - Olin Class photo Tufts whole grad class, 2011; MS247.001586 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - First graduating students and guests Reception, 2011 May 20; MS247.001587 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - OKU Awards dinner, 2011 May 20; MS247.001588 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      178 frames large index
    - Dental commencement, 2011 May 22; MS247.001589 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      mark special
    - Grad School Hooding Aidekman, 2011 May 21; MS247.001590 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      149 images
    - Tufts Dental Lonnie flip book "Goodbyes", 2011 May 13; MS247.001591 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Last awards dinner Copley Westin
      Lonnie Norris; School of Dental Medicine
    - SNDA Awards Dinner, 2011 May 17; MS247.001592 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      113 images
    - H D A Awards Dinner, 2011 May 18; MS247.001593 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      83 images
    - fr student reception, 2011 May 20; MS247.001594 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      3 frames chosen
    - TUD Surgery Dinner Top of the Hub, 2011 June 27; MS247.001595 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      138 images
    - Medford Grad School Grad Awards, 2012; MS247.001596 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      193 frames
    - Grad Schools Auditorium Awards ceremony, 2012; MS247.001597 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Not hooding!
    - TUD Senior Awards Dinner, 2012 May 11; MS247.001598 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Dental dinner at Westin Copley 245 frames
    - TUD Sr Awards, 2002 May 11; MS247.001599 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - OKU, 2012 May 18; MS247.001600 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Graduation, 2012 May 20; MS247.001601 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - SNDA, 2012 May 15; MS247.001602 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      B20497
    - TUD Awards Lunch, circa 2012; MS247.001603 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Dental Family Welcome Day, 2012 August 27; MS247.001604 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      unedited right from camera card backup
    - Tufts Dental Family Welcome Day, 2012 August 27; MS247.001605 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Color corrected disc
    - TUD Family Day Dr Buchanan, 2012 August 27; MS247.001606 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      extra attention color corrected
    - Dental Staff Awards Ice Cream Social, 2012 September 7; MS247.001607 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      114 pix
      Christine Robertson; Boston Campus; School of Dental Medicine
    - Hooding Tufts Graduate School, 2013; MS247.001608 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      back up disc no edits
    - Tufts Dental Commencement, 2013 May 19; MS247.001609 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bates Awards Dinner, 2013 May 15; MS247.001610 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      188 frames backup unedited
    - Dental Recognition Lunch Dr. Morton Rosenberg headshots, 2008 August 8; MS247.001611 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Farah Pandith disc II, circa 2008; MS247.001612 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Medford Campus; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - Tufts Dental Dr. Wanda Wright, 2008 May 7; MS247.001613 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Favored frames 22,69,133, 136,146, 156
    - Tufts Libraries Author Talk Felipe Fernandez-Arnesto, 2008 February 13; MS247.001614 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Libraries Author Talk Felipe Fernandez-Arnesto, 2008 February 13; MS247.001615 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - David Valdes Greenwood Tisch Author Talk, 2008 November 12; MS247.001616 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Homo Domesticus a little fruitcake
    - Yankee Dental disc I, 2008 February; MS247.001617 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Yankee Dental disc II, 2008 February; MS247.001618 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Police Awards Ceremony, 2008 September 25; MS247.001619 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Alumnae Lounge with flags
    - D10 White Coat ceremony disc A, 2008 March 15; MS247.001620 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - D10 White Coat ceremony disc B, 2008 March 15; MS247.001621 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bates Day, 2008 March 12; MS247.001622 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Jason Lacourse
    - Bates Day, 2008 March 12; MS247.001623 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Faculty Practice Portraits, 2008 March; MS247.001624 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      black background
    - Women in Science, Medicine Engineering, 2008 April 4; MS247.001625 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Mildred Dresselhaus ( MIT)
      Jamshed Bharucha; Peggy Newell; Medford Campus
    - Tufts Dental 08 Student Practices, 2008; MS247.001626 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Commencement, 2008 May 08; MS247.001627 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Disc A 3892
    - Dental Commencement, 2008 May 08; MS247.001628 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Disc B 3893
    - Dental Reunion disc A, 2008; MS247.001629 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      1-250
      Allison Norton; School of Dental Medicine
    - Dental Reunion disc B, 2008; MS247.001630 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      251-500
    - Dental Reunion disc C, 2008; MS247.001631 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      501-656
    - Dental Surgery Dinner at Radios., 2008 June 25; MS247.001632 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      135 pictures
    - H D A Dinner Awards Dinner, 2008 May 12; MS247.001633 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Hispanic Awards Dinner
    - Graduate Hooding, 2008 May 17; MS247.001634 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      001-184
    - Dental Awards Dinner, 2008 May 09; MS247.001635 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Pam Goldberg's Entrepreneurship Competition, 2008; MS247.001636 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      classic and social with directors meetingand Awards ceremony
    - Rapmaster Jonathan Garlick OKU Dinner, 2008; MS247.001637 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Surgery Dinner at Radios., 2008 June 25; MS247.001638 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Recognition Lunch disc I, 2008; MS247.001639 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Recognition Lunch disc II, 2008; MS247.001640 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Class of 2010 International White coat, 2008 July 23; MS247.001641 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Rolls 1-4
    - D 12 Family Welcome Day, 2008 August 26; MS247.001642 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      176-314
    - D 12 Family Welcome Day, 2008 August 26; MS247.001643 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      001-175
    - Wide Open disc I, 2008; MS247.001644 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      frames 0001-0175
    - Wide Open disc II, 2008; MS247.001645 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      frames 0176-0334
    - Dental: Chinese Dinner, 2008; MS247.001646 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Disc # 26 "overflow" disc
    - SNDA Awards Dinner, 2008 May 14; MS247.001647 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      001-148
    - Cancer Research Day disc I, 2008 October 17; MS247.001648 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Cancer Research Day disc II, 2008 October 17; MS247.001649 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Professor of the Semester 1st award, 2008 November 6; MS247.001650 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Mike Thompson's expression
    - Tufts First Circle Event Langham Hotel, 2008 October 26; MS247.001651 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Rob Hollister greetings to new office
    - Leslie new asst to Dr Briss, circa 2000s; MS247.001652 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      13 prints
    - Sam Cornish, 2009; MS247.001653 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Yankee Dental 09 disc B, 2009; MS247.001654 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Yankee Dental 09 disc A, 2009; MS247.001655 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Tisch Author Talk Susan Napier, 2009 February 20; MS247.001656 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Anima/Manga Prof. Japanese Studies
    - Mark Gonthier's emergency shoot of GLB at Hall Bulletin, 2009 March 5; MS247.001657 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 4th annual Balmuth, 2009 February 24; MS247.001658 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Andrew Wilson Oxford Chase dining and Cabot
    - Senior Dental Awards Dinner, 2009 May 8; MS247.001659 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      175 prints
    - Bates Andrews 09, 2009; MS247.001660 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Gentle Dental Team Picture, 2009 April 1; MS247.001661 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Becker
    - Tufts A and S Graduate School, 2009; MS247.001662 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bates Andrews Dinner, 2009 May 12; MS247.001663 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Friends and Deval Patrick at Tufts Dental Commencement, 2009 May 17; MS247.001664 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Grad hooding disc A, 2009; MS247.001665 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Grad hooding disc B, 2009; MS247.001666 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Grad: Dental 2009 disc A, MS247.001667 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Tufts Grad: Dental 2009 disc B, MS247.001668 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Class of 13 Family Welcome Event, 2009; MS247.001669 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      1st at Emerson Majestic
    - SNDA Dinner, 2009; MS247.001670 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Oral Surgery Dinner, 2009 June 24; MS247.001671 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Marylin Peterson
    - Research Day Global Health and Infectious Disease, 2009 October 5; MS247.001672 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dental Faculty Recognition Luncheon, 2009 August 7; MS247.001673 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Donna McDaniel and Vanessa Julye Tisch Author Talk, 2009 November 12; MS247.001674 (Box 7, Folder 5)